CHU Fong, (Candice)

SAU MAU PING, KOWLOON

TEL: 54977921

Email: candicechu126@gmail.com

PROFILE

My experiences had given me strong organizational abilities, an analytical approach to projects and the capacity to operate under pressure. I aim to learn something new from every experience since I feel there is always space for personal and professional growth.

SKILLS & ABILITIES

- Good communication
- Excellent conceptual and analytical skills
- Effective interpersonal
- Software & Platform

(Visual Studio, Arduino, App Inventor,

Game Maker, MySQL, React Native)

Program Language

(HTML, JavaScript, C#, C++, Python ...)

Office Software

(Word, Excel, PowerPoint...)

LANGUAGES

- Cantonese (Native)
- Mandarin (Native)
- English (Intermediate)

AREAS EXPERTISE

- Website Design
- Mobile App Design
- Circuit Design
- Hardware and Software Project

EXPERIENCE

Research and Techer Assistant (Part-time)

Youth Global Network (Sept 1, 2021 - Now)

Assist in software maintenance of youCodia products

> STEM Assistant Coordinator Intern

Youth Global Network (Jun 1, 2021-August 30, 2021)

- Support of software platform and design recommendation
- Test education platform

Quality Analyst- Web/Mobile Application Intern

JoyAether Limited (Dec 23, 2020 - Feby 3, 2021)

- Business Information Collection
- Web / Mobile Application Testing

Computer Engineering Intern - Programmer

mSolution Consultants Limited (Dec 2018 – Apr 2019)

- Analysis the problem from the CCTV situation of the site
- Conducted research bases on python method to compare two image similarity
- Design program and virtual database

EDUCATION

2019-2022

Hong Kong University of Science and Technology, Bachelor In Electronic Engineering (Y4)

HONOR & AWARDS

- Pearson LCCI Certificate (HKVEP)
- Leadership and commitment Gold certificate
- IVElite sharing on student Learning Outcomes
- American Women's Association Scholarship
- Rotary club of Channel Islands Scholarship

ACTIVITY

- Red Cross Health Management Volunteer
- Electronic and Computer engineering Students' Society member (Position: Internal Vice-Chairperson)